

DHAVAL LAL

Full Stack Developer

About Me

I have Completed MCA In 2017 And I Would Like To Work On Live Project. I Would Like To Work As A Back End Developer. I Know About Git & Github, HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, JavaScript. JQuery, Bootstrap, PHP And MySql. Also I Have Some Knowledge About Laravel Framework.



+91 89806 28004



dhavallal231025@gmail.com



Rajkot, India

Language

- English
- Gujarati
- Hindi

Expertise

- Management Skills
- Creativity
- Digital Marketing
- Negotiation
- Critical Thinking
- Leadership

Experience

Om College

Rajkot - India

2018 - 2019

I had work as professor at om College and teaching all subject in BCA like c language Android Java c++ Data Structure and many more and I also manage computer lab.

Online Module

Rajkot - India

2020 - 2022

In 2020 I had taught many students in online Module due to corona (Lock-down) I had taught all IT subjects and also web development.

Speed Computers

Sydney - India

2022 - Current

I am working in speed computers as a professor I am teaching web development and IT subjects and I also create website for speed computers so I am also interested in web development.

Education

Saurashtra University (S.U)

Bachelor of Computer Application 2013 - 2015 (80%)

Gujarat Technological University (G.T.U)

Master of Computer Application 2015 - 2017 (9.17 CGPA)

Skills Summary

Design Process

78 %

Project Management

81 %